

	https://th.linkedin.com/in/vitalii-nikiforov-3b404159
$\vee$	underscorevint@gmail.com
	underscorevint
0	Thailand, (UTC + 7)

### **PROFILE**

I have been involved in Design field professionally for over 15 years. I'm creative, pixel-perfect specialist with ability and I'm using my artistic talent, my other skills and previous experience at the max during my working process. These circumstances are reason for providing an amazing result with any kind of tasks. Usually I'm serving as a UX / UI / Visual Designer and I'm responsible for all processes of digital product's creation, starting from idea and following through wireframing and prototype to the launch.

As a team member I had been worked in collaboration with UI engineers and lead the other designers. I was worked on graphics for the different startups such us: trading platforms (forex, forex currency exchange), b2b / b2c geo location system with complex investment's statistics for country regions, wide types of web apps, mobile apps and games. My responsibilities included creating user interfaces, wireframes, web apps / mobile apps' prototypes, illustrations, game graphic and corporate identity.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2013 - Present time

Freelance Digital Designer, Self employed

January 2011 - December 2013

Senior UX / UI Designer, Swapforex.com LLC

September 2010 - January 2011

Visual Designer, Phereo.com

April 2010 - September 2010 Art Director, *OOO Sovetnik* 

September 2009 - March 2010

Art Director, ETS Baltica LLC

January 2009 - September 2009

UX / UI Designer, OOO Dnevnik.ru

November 2007 - September 2009

Senior Designer, E-ngineers

September 2004 - March 2007

Web Designer, Kyozou Inc

November 2001 - September 2004 Web Designer, *UG Design Studio* 

# SKILLS

	NEWBIE								EXPERT	
User Interfaces			1	1	1	1	1	1	1	•
User Experience			1	1	1	1	1		•	
Graphic Design			1	1	1	1	1	1	1	•
Corporate identity			1	1	1	1	1		•	
Illustrations			1	1	1	1	1	1	1	•
Prototyping			,	1	1		,	1	1	•
HTML & CSS			1	1	1	1	1	1	1	•

### **EDUCATION**

1986 - 1993

Local Art School

1996 - 2001

Alexander Mozhaysky Military Space Academy

Banchelor's Degree in Information Technologies & Networks

# **PORTFOLIO**

http://www.underscorevint.com/portfolio.pdf http://www.dribbble.com/underscorevint